let me tell y'all what y'all sound like when I was interviewed by Shannon Sharp
they cut a part of the interview out and the part of the interview that they cut out was
he asked me um about OJ Simpson who had just passed away and he said that I guess one of
the members of Nicole Brown Simpson's family had like said something disparaging about OJ Simpson
and you know I guess he was asking me like what I felt about that and I say you know you gonna
feel how you feel just like when Queen Elizabeth passed away folks who have you know lived in her
colonies and who are descendants and have experienced um British colonization was like
ding dong the witch is dead and he was like oh yeah you know I would never I would never I was
like so let me just get this straight if you went back in time to attend the funeral of your
ancestors slave master you telling me that you would shed a tear that you would be silent and
that you would hold respect and space for them well you know I was raised you know I was just
ready to respect the dead that's how y'all sound y'all sound like folks who would bring flowers to
mass's funeral support a real one
you